Lescaze, Alexandra UNITE Cannon Fieldcrest Organizing Files 6362
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Alexandra Lescaze UNITE Cannon Fieldcrest Organizing Files
1962- 2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lescaze, Alexandra
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
Cannon Fieldcrest
Pillowtex
6362
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
8254229
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 27, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619/007: ACTWU Organizing Department Files 6000/039: UNITE Organizing Department Records 6362 AV: Alexandra Lescaze UNITE Cannon Fieldcrest Organizing Audio-Visual Materials 6362 P: Alexandra Lescaze UNITE Cannon Fieldcrest Organizing Photographs
Lescaze, Alexandra; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Cannon Fieldcrest; Pillowtex; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees
8254229
- Historical Background, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cannon Mills History, 1985-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Chronologies, 1982-1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Calendars, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Campaign Research, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cannon Historical Resources, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cabarrus County, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Kannapolis Case Study and Bibliography, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- KPS Report on Pillowtex, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Unite! History, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Campaign Planning, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Organizing Directors, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Get Out the Vote Organizing Meeting Packet, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Sample ACTWU Sign-Up Card (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Captive Audience Speech, Cannon Plant, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Report on Cannon Campaign, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Charles Sallee Letter to Organizing Directors, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Media Campaign Memo, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- David Murdock Political Activities, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Ballots and Surveys, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Pillowtex Conference Call, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Fieldcrest Cannon Label Samples (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Notes (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Pillowtex Visitor's Badge (Box 1, Folder 24)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1991-2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Kannapolis: City of Looms Sign-up, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Victory is Ours Draft (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Union Congressional Endorsement, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- What is Fieldcrest's Answer to Rate Cuts and Workload Increases?, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- What is the Company Hiding? (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Cannon Mills Sold, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Cannon Workers Demand Union Election, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Mortgaged! To Buy Foreign Imports, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Welcome to the Reading of Fieldcrest's Confession (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Cannon Housing, 1984-1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Get Out the Vote Lists and Handouts, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Area Maps, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Letters of Support from Other Unions, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Cannon Press Packet, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Worker Statements, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Cannon Retirement Plan, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- NLRB Required Notice Regarding Union Organizing (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Labor Law: Handbook for Organizing Unions, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Textile Voices: Songs from the Mills, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- A Visit to Cannon Mills (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Women, Restructuring, and Textiles (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Prayer for Fieldcrest Cannon Workers (Box 1, Folder 47)
- The Dark Side of the Force: A Case Study of Restructuring and Social Capital, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Prospects of a Southern Textile Union, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Rebel Pen: Writings of Mary Heaton Vorse (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Unions Change Lives, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- A Song for Bob Freeman (Box 1, Folder 52)